[man1] so you’re thinking about these 2 shoes right here? [man2] yeah right here those
[man1] all right you need a 13?
[man2] either 12.5 or 13
[man1]  wanna try 12.5 first [man2] yeah
[man2]  that’ll probably be the easiest route
[man1] can he try out 12.5 of both of these
[man2]  these are really comfortable but I think this is [man1] they feel a little too big? [man2] I feel my heel slipping in the back  [man1] [inaudible] yeah  the only thing is you’re still growing so that wouldn’t be too bad [man2] and also my foot is probably gonna grow by Christmas  [man1] yeah like you are only 12 years old so [man2] yeah
[man1] aaa it would be like like I wouldn’t buy those I’m not growing anymore so Jordan Trainer 1 Low wants to be comfortable one pair of shoe down ohooo oh what are you doing [man2] I’m looking at the price tag [man1] ain’t no price tag ain’t  no price tag jus caught what you’re looking at man [man2]  ok
[man2]  that’s tight as can be!
[man1] oh so you’re gonna be growing too [man2] yeah [man1]  how’s that [man2]  large  cause a 12 year old boy you know they’ll be growing super fast [man2] I’m supposed to grow 4inches every year [man1] yeah that’s crazy as hell  [man1] oh that’s nice [man2] yeah it won’t look too tight  [inaudible]