[man] so hey crew we’re just coming to check you out because the girls they’re getting ready for our vacation
[inaudible] [man] to San Antonio
[man] Riley why are you running around come and sit down
[man]  but they’re getting for our vacation in San Antonio so they’re about to pack their luggage [kid1]  yea [man] they got their clothes spread all the way out for what  I don’t know
[man] so it seems like they are ready [kid1]  no, we’re not [kid2]  dad I need scissors [man] no you don’t [kid2]   ok
[man] you want me to show you daddy strength
[kid2] thanks [man] here [inaudible]
[man]  try  it
[man] this is daddy strength
[man] you see how I don’t need anything [kid2] yes [man] here you go [kid2] I don’t wanna [inaudible] myself that’s why [man] I don’t wanna hear that [inaudible]  Riley want me to break yours [kid1] yeah [man] ok so hold it [inaudible]