okay so you're going to come over here you're going to stand behind this hot box
kids please
BFF
are you going to touch it
Doom 3 Bob had to sounded like my mom Hunter magic classes on Cooper eyeball power to Candyland what is this called
I reach and this is actually called the lever you're going to turn into a human Sita there's not one of my hand someone on my feet I'm going to Lower Town play the piano try not to drop this back like Nevada is it up you want to act right and then I'm going to come back
get over here Mister the used in here
step over that lava into the Magic Water
to come back over one foot
oh he did play the piano and come back
and then the end of the world
yes