now you ready for the party and for added strength he can do a handstand against the wall
drawing
Supertramp forget your fingers you get to do it
I don't want to see if you can count to 10 what's your up to very important parents to have them look at their fingers
that was amazing how are you so strong how did you get the pizza
baby boomers
oh he did tell me push can you show us a picture and see if you can do mine
oh my gosh we have push-up now you can also try the lever hey if you want to really get good at it and be really really think before you go to the floor get out of the car when I step over The Lava one let her get that back leg up hands on the couch and then you can hop here
and then stand back up and then you can make the lower and lower and lower until eventually you're able to do this seesaw piano without popping onto your hands
already