Harkins it
DirecTV
by then this is a hard decision they're both pretty awesome chair and Ryan share is higher than daddy with a Daddy chair look like a King's throne so I think the winter around to share building contest goes to Daddy
Play-Doh time
1.4 Ryan 1.4.
Brown 3 will decide the winner Let's do an animal this time let's do a giraffe be ready
okay guys 5 minutes is that Messi your direct creation tall giraffe neck you got going on there buddy
hey he sure can grab all the food from the tree I what you got over there daddy
what is that kind of cancer watching does this look like a giraffe really look like a giraffe I'm sorry so Ryan is the winner of
TV stand on