[kids singing]
[ma] all right, good morning moustaches
[kids] good morning, Mister Jeff
[man] after our greeting, we always have time to
[kids] to share
[man] all right have a sit
[kid] [inaudible]
[kid] do you know of
[kid] inaudible
[kid] what the best is it
[nothing]
[kid] hi
[man] hi
[man] so do we look at when we care
[kids] sometimes to who's talking
[man] where are our hands
[kids] in our laps
[man] right, remember if you are the person who is sharing
[man] then what do you need to do
[kids] sing aloud
[man] all right, we'll start with Diermine
[nothing]
[boy] yesterday I was at my dad's house
[man] questions for Diermine
[man] Mia
[girl] what did you do over your dad's house
[boy] yesterday I was at my dad's house to aa
[boy] inaudible