[man] anymore questions? Analysse
[girl] did you watch TV?
[girl] maybe a little bit
[boy] I don't have a TV and
[boy] and we never watch TV
[man] why did you go to your dad's house?
[boy] aa because we had to wth, my mom came with us one more day
[boy] is my dad will call the police on you because if we had [inaudible]
[boy] [inaudible]
[boy] my mom won't see me my dad
[man] thank you Dierman for sharing
[boy] thing about my dad is that
[boy] we do have to go to see
[man] ok
[boy] very very good
[man] so you don't have to go or you do have to go
[boy] don't
[man] ok
[boy] because well it's is very good
[boy] I have to walk I don't I don't  have to get [inaudible] I don't  I don't  even have to like it
[boy] my hand
[man] very good, thank you Dierman for sharing all right
[man] Liaaa
[kid] inaudible
[girl] I [inaudible]