[girl1] now what is this  [girl2] I don't know what this is  [girl1] eee [inaudible] [girl2] abc
[girl2] a is it a
[girl1] and what is this
[girl2] r [girl1] no
[girl 2] aaa [girl1] abcd
[girl2] yes  a haha I just said a
[girl1] hahaha all right [girls1]  we finish work mom [inaudible] [woman] go put away the book
[inaudible] [girl 2] that the last one how do you feel [girl 2] how do you feel  haha [inaudible] [girl 2] again
[girl1] yeah how do you feel [girl2] good
[girl1] ok stop [girl2] ok how do you feel
[girl2] not good [girl1] no how do you feel
[girl2] ok [girl1] no how do you feel
[girl2] good [girl1] all right take off this [girl2] haha [inaudible] mommy look what [inaudible] is doing
[inaudible] [girl1] hey all right how do you feel  haha how do you feel how do you feel how do you feel
[girl1]  how do you feel
[girl2] good good [inaudible]
[girl2] good
[girl1] oh ha happy are you happy [girl2] yeah [girl1] haha when I said are you happy you said yeah
[inaudible] [girl1] no no this doesn't [inaudible]