[woman] let it go let it go  [inaudible] can you put that down there
[kid] can we put some more
[inaudible] [woman] not yet
[woman] we got a mommy [inaudible] pot [kid] yes [woman] let me get a daddy [inaudible] pot [kid] ay
[woman] hold the [inaudible] put it there oh ha
[woman] catch fingers did you [inaudible] good boy [inaudible]  [kid] a bit more [woman] a bit more  yeah [inaudible]  [woman] oh clever boy [kid] a bit more [woman] a bit more yeah
[woman] clever boy [inaudible]
[woman] can you tap the bottom ok [inaudible]  hold it there [kid] push it down [woman] wait wait wait [inaudible]  a little bit now
[woman] ok a bit of water
[woman] [inaudible]  very good of water that's enough that's enough ok now [kid] need some more
[woman] add some more yeah
[woman] be very careful not too much [inaudible] give her a [inaudible] for me that's enough that's enough
[inaudible] [woman] just just careful careful [inaudible]
[kid] aaa haha
[woman] no [inaudible] haha put it there
[woman] what's that [inaudible]
[kid] I love my [inaudible] pots