[woman] hi are you curious? he's filming
[woman] he's filming [girl] where did that goes
[woman] what should we do with this?
[woman] should I put it here [boy] yeah [woman]  ok are you gonna come work here
[girl] where did that goes [woman] let's see that's the woman the fire woman can you find the fire woman?
[inaudible]
[woman] [inaudible] turn it turn it on the puzzle board can you try turn it out like that [girl] yes [woman] give it a try  the top of the hat is up here can you match the tops [girl] I did [woman] is that working [inaudible] ok
[woman] [inaudible] it does match
[woman] it matches oh all right
[girl] where that goes [woman] [inaudible] [girl] where that goes [woman] that's part of the ladder and part of the rack on the top look Angela
[woman] you did it you did it high five