[woman] Is it cold today? Let me see if it’s cold does that mean we could wear you have to tell me what we can wear can
[woman] Can we wear swimsuit today? [kids] no
[kids] ha ha  [woman] Do we need an umbrella today? [kids] no [woman] ok what do you think we need? [kid1] a jacket [woman] a jacket? how about a heavy coat?
[woman] and on here what do you have? [inaudible]
[inaudible] [girl1] I have a heavy coat [woman] you have a heavy coat? Good I’m glad to hear that Marissa that’s a good things to wear today mitten who has mittens today ? kid2] not me
[woman] no no mittens ok well think about going outside because [inaudible]  ok [inaudible]  [kids] mittens
[woman] you do? Good, you have mittens today too? That’s smart move
[woman]  ok which do you want hand or the apple? Ok take the hand
[woman] here we go all right what’s our first number?
[kids] zero [woman] zero very good guys zero
[kids] [woman] one two [woman] let’s go to this one first [kids]  one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen [woman] ooo
[woman]  do we really have 17 kids ?
[kids] no [woman] Lupita I’m gonna move you back over  ok? Here we go
[woman] let’s count one more time [kid3] fourteen  [woman] Very good Peter thank you fourteen kids we’ve got fourteen kids today
[woman] Do you wanna tell everybody
[woman] you don’t wanna say we have fourteen kids in class?
[woman]  Can you do that? Ok that’s all right