[woman] Diana Lowestein child and family therapist
in Toronto Canada
[woman] Today I’m going to show an activity  called bubbles, and this is an activity to help children learn pro social behavior
[woman] and I have my daughter Jamie and our friend Josh
[woman] who are going to help me demonstrate this activity.
[woman]  The rules of this game are:
[woman]  we’re going to take turns blowing bubble. Do you guys like to blow bubbles
[girl] yeah [woman] Do you guys like to blow bubbles  yeah so
[woman] we’re gonna take turns and everyone’s going to have a turn and here are the rules you have to follow in order to get a turn
[woman] you have to first  wait your turn, that’s the first rule The second rules is when it is your turn you’re gonna say Please may I have the bubbles?
[woman] When you get the bubbles you’re going to thank the person who gave the bubbles by saying thank you for giving me the bubbles and then when is your turn you get three turns to blow bubbles
[woman] and you’re not gonna blow bubbles at anyone’s faces we’re gonna blow bubbles that way so we don't
[woman]  so the bubbles don’t go to anyone’s faces
[woman]  and then the other rule is we’re gonna share by passing so when your turn is finished when you're gonna blow bubbles 3 times finished then you’re gonna pass to the person the next in case you don’t remember all those rules I’m gonna remind you as we go along [boy] she can go first
[woman] aww that’s very nice you’re already learning  very nice behavior, that’s very nice what do you wanna say
[girl] thank you Josh