[woman]  what I need you to tell me which glass has more or if they have the same?
[woman] Has more? Ok they have the same now? That one has more ?
[woman] Are they equal now
[woman] ok how about if I pour this one into this one? Now which one has more ? Why? [girl] [inaudible]
[woman]  all right which one do they have the same amount of juice [girl] no [woman] which one has more?
[woman] That one does? Ok
[woman] do they have the same amount now oh how about if I pour this one into this cup
[woman] which one has more now? Why?
[girl] because it’s [inaudible]
[woman]  all right ok all right
[woman] do [inaudible] have the same amount of juice? [boy] yes [woman]  are you sure what if I pour this one into this one? Do they have the same amount of juice now?
[boy] no