take all the pieces out you can put them here or here while you take them out
you going to hold them all that is that one
it looks like part of the letter and part of the Rat Pack
that's the area you might have to turn it
turn it on the puzzle board until it fits into place
that's the right area the steps of the ladder are going this way
so you turn it to match the direction the steps are going poster for almost there turn up that way that working out for you
did you catch this a good idea to put what in places and see
give it a try it looks like more of the ladder
Legos I see that it's got a fireman and a half and a eyes and nose and mouth so what other one has fireman's with eyes and nose and mouth
can you match it
Atlanta