Alexis is there more cranberry juice in this glass or cranberry juice in this class or do they have the same amount
the same amount of can I watch this is what we're going to do
now is there more cranberry juice in this class more cranberry juice in this class or do they have the same amount of life and why do you think this one has more because you don't go
damn that that it's just an amount it's just, so is there more in this class or more in this class or are they the same amount and just got the tire
so they have the same amount
how do you know they have the same amount
because when when when
because because this was bigger okay so does this one have more does this one have more or do they have the same amount
kfvs12
so this one has more or they have the same amount still
just want it and how why do you think this one has more because it's taller what what if we pour this back in here
the thing and now it's the same amount so what if we pour this back in here
let's try to cut glass more cranberry juice in glass or do they have the same amount
because of Todd