ready for this cookie girl chocolate chips
you can taste the chocolate chip
so good right
Batgirl no more okay now we need one egg Vivianne Decker no more hand right on your lap like to be really crazy with our jobs but there's nothing that gives me more joy than spending time with my babies like a very mischievous she messes with me and her daddy and her brother all the time
I don't want you to get salmonella girl
no you don't trust me
do you know who gave me this this cuz it was for me and Daddy's wedding when we got married and that's so nice
yeah it's not time for you to be married
baby are you going to marry
you can you can marry while you could stay with me forever if you want