now we're going to add a half now when your hands hit are we going to do noodle arms or PetSmart
is it you do it try and you told me he might try you push on me is that a pencil
now do it again is that a pencil
okay you're almost there we're almost to the end now you're going to step over
been always a big pain in your lines look for your what what do we look for kids
that's four fingers and you're going to lift your legs up and stand up I put a lunch Walmart
big step over with for those fingers hands right here and her little mouth talk so perfect and artist
I keep your foot straight beat kids you want to go straight on the freeway you don't want to be critical and he sending the big men's very important now he's going to try the other Life trailer
you can do it
deaf lunch or boil your food for your fingers go ahead and get ready to play the piano
where's my house and look for your fingers and hold on I'm texting his back legs up kids and then the back foot goes back to yours yes