Paisley will you dance for me sweetie can you show me how you did on the couch
May 2nd
shake your booty shake your booty shake your booty
what's your favorite food Paisley
your favorite food do you know mac and cheese mac and cheese I like mac and cheese to Yummy Yummy what do you do when you go to bed to read a story do you like what you do and read a story to story do they talk to you in
yeah the turkey on your bed yet
did I do something called cheetah
what's Tito I'm cheetah
no I'm not I'm Mickey your Mickey and I'm cheetah
Witchita Google I know who's Tito
oh and she don't got it Mickey Mickey
that was funny yeah was funny yes he does